Amani Qenaai

CERTIFIED OF SECURITY ANALYIST

PROFILE

I have gained experience in many realms of the IT field including help desk, ERP System Cyber Security life cycle, audit while committed to protecting IT and Monitoring, SharePoint/Website Development, Programming languages Java and Python

EDUCATION

Saudi Arabia, Jubail industrial University

Computer science and engineering bachelor's degree 2017

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office 365 App
- Office Security & Compliance
- Helpdesk Software
- ERP Oracle EBS
- SharePoint
- website
- Teamwork and Communication
- Ability to work under pressure.

LANGUAGES

English - **Excellent** Arabic -Native

CONTACT



0537305659



amanigenaai@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Security Specialist -2019 to today

Mange the security performance platform of Infrastructure, networks, Software, Hardware, Data, System, Application. Monitoring, Analysis unusual and suspicious activities. Perform audit and how the users implement the Polices & procedures, and identity user access control and identity to ensure security practices are compliant. Working on website development and SharePoint

Technical consult and supportfreelancer work-2018 - 2019

IT Transformation Officer/Codiet, Eastern Province-2017-2018

Trying successfully changing the methods of education in government schools to E-leaning "Future Gate Project"

IT Admin/Jubail University College-2016-2017

Upgrade and update operating system of devices, Repair network cable, Provide support for technical issues to software and hardware during office hours